Guide to the Collection of Bookplates by Edwin Davis French
Yale University Arts Library
- Box Listing
  - Twentieth Century Club, 1898; 7 (Box 8, Folder 235)
    Includes one signed print; letter dated 1898.
  - U-sepe-ars-so-ap, 1893; 8 (Box 8, Folder 236)
  - Union League Club (NY), 1900 1904; 18 (Box 8, Folder 237)
    Includes one early state; letter to Miss Merrill from William Bradford Child dated September 26, 1904.
  - University Club (Cleveland), 1900; 7 items (Box 8, Folder 238)
  - Utica Public Library, 1906; 7 (Box 8, Folder 239)
  - Vail, Davis Righter and Henry H., 1905; 6 items (Box 8, Folder 240)
  - Van Wagenen, Frederick W., 1898; 3 (Box 8, Folder 241)
  - Varnum, James A., 1902; 13 items (Box 8, Folder 242)
    Includes eight signed prints; copperplate; ephemera.
  - Vassar Alumnae Historical Association, 1898; 6 (Box 8, Folder 243)
  - Warner, Beverly, 1894; 8 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    Includes two signed prints; newspaper clipping.
  - Washington County Free Library, 1902; 15 items (Box 8, Folder 245)
    Includes three trial proofs.
  - W. H. and K. T. B., undated; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 246)
  - Welsh, Gertrude Clarkson, 1904; 5 (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Wendell, Barrett, 1898; 8 (Box 8, Folder 248)
    Includes one signed print; newspaper article; letter from B. W. dated November 14, 1898.
  - Westcott, Elizabeth T., 1910; 6 (Box 8, Folder 249)
    Includes three prints signed by A. J. Brown, Sc.
  - Whitin, Sarah Elizabeth, 1901; 5 (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Willets, Howard, 1896; 5 (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Williams, E. P. and John S., 1898 1899; 12 (Box 8, Folder 252)
    Includes photograph of Mrs. John Skelton Williams.
  - Winslow, Wynne, 1902; 3 (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Winthrop, Henry Rogers, 1898; 14 items (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Wodell, Silas, 1900; 5 (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Wood, Arnold, 1898 1899; 15 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Wood, Ethel H. and W. C., undated; 16 items (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Woodbury, John Page, 1894 1903; 23 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    Includes five signed prints; one trial proof; two prints signed by John P. Woodbury; letter to Mrs. Mary E. Roth-Merrill from John P. Woodbury dated August 4, 1903.
  - Woodward, S. Walter, 1901; 5 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Worcester Art Museum, The, 1901; 9 (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Yale Club of New York, undated; 31 items (Box 8, Folder 261)
    Includes three prints signed by Howard Pyle.